And they used AI to bring the drawing
that the kid was just finished drawing,
bring it to life. And this gave the kids
excitement and something to be proud of
that they were running to their parents
to be proud. Look what I did. They saw
that, "Hey, this app that my kid is
using is not just spending time on
another app. It's like very positive
screen time. They could see the value of
the app." So, when we introduced this
during first time user experience, it
really increased output. Because parents
could really understand, "Hey, this
product worth me investing in it."
>> Hello, I'm your host David Bernard. And
with me today, Remi CEO Jacob Eiting.
Our guest today is Yoav Sharon, head of
growth and product at Simply.
Simply is a world's leading creativity
companion for the home. On the Pie cast,
we talk with Yoav about reaching brand
new audiences through web funnels,
[snorts]
how they created their own Big Mac Index
for global pricing,
and why monthly plans can beat annual on
LTV. Hey Yoav, thanks so much for
joining us on the Pie cast today.
>> Thank you for having me and happy to be
here. Looking forward to chat.
>> I I thought it'd be helpful to get a a
quick overview. Uh Simply does a lot and
I and to have context for the rest of
the conversation, it'd be great to just
hear a little about about what y'all do.
>> Sounds good. Um maybe I'll start with a
very easy question. Does any of you play
any musical instrument?
>> Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. I can't see it in
the shot here, but my guitar's hanging
on the wall. I mean, I I I call it my
it's my aspirational guitar cuz it gets
it gets looked at a lot more than it
gets played, but but it's there.
>> Uh I I took classical piano lessons
growing up.
>> Yeah, David's actually more of a
musician I think than than than me, but
>> You used to be. Used to be more of a
musician.
>> Used to be. That's also accurate for me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> So, it's it's actually so familiar what
you're saying and inspirational is a
word. Basically, um
Simply is about helping
kids and adults around the world learn
creative hobbies.
Learn how to play
piano, how to play the guitar, how to
gain confidence in singing, how to
express themselves through drawing.
And all of these and again, like you you
saying inspirational and you said you
pick it up maybe as a kid, it's always
some kind of a dream. It's quite hard to
learn these new skills.
So, what Simply is doing is we're
breaking up to small chunks each of the
pedagogical
way and we help people through all the
challenges and we really um make dreams
come true in this aspect. We help people
across the world learn their
musical instrument that what they've
been dreaming on since kids. Um and it's
really exciting exciting things to do.
>> I I love it. I when I learned guitar
initially, I was like maybe 12 and and I
did it with via I can't remember the
name of the software, but some piece of
boxed software I got from Staples.
Uh
>> Oh, wow.
>> Cuz there was no YouTube, Jacob. There
wasn't a Yeah, there was no App Store.
There was I went to I drove to the town
over and I probably paid $45 for a box
of software that taught me to play
guitar. So, like I've I've I might be
one of the like early digital like
musician musical natives, right?
But uh but I've always been sold on the
concept since then cuz it actually I
actually did learn guitar sitting at my
desktop PC with that piece of software.
Yeah, it's crazy.
>> This is fantastic. So, they basically
we're able to bring a coach almost at a
coach level next to you uh to be with
you as you learn all these skills and
all these hobbies. It will get right
into all of these uh but this is in big
we have
in general I mentioned we have a a
Simply Piano, our most mature app. We
have Simply Guitar and Simply Sing. And
Simply Draw was the recent app that
joined.
Across all of them, we we are active
with million users and learners around
the world.
>> Wow.
>> Um 11 languages, 180 countries. So,
we're quite at the interesting scale at
this point.
>> That's actually where I did want to
start is the multi-app portfolio. So, I
actually had the chief product officer
from Duolingo on the podcast earlier
this year, and he talked about how they
tried to launch multiple learning apps
and and ended up pulling it back in.
I've heard from a lot of other people
who struggled to do the portfolio
approach.
>> Oh, David, do you know that Elevate
story? Like before we did Elevate, like
we had it was originally a company
called MindSnacks. We had like
10 different language distinct language
It was a nightmare. Like it I mean, it
was It just It's hard. Like technically,
right? And just everything is very
>> And and promotion
>> like like having to get people to 10
different apps. And you think you think
like, "Oh, they download the main app
and then we push them to the other
apps." But that doesn't always work.
>> Economies of scale are a lot rarer than
people think, right?
>> Not only this, basically, when you have
your first mature app and it's already
at scale,
getting to the second app is more than
finding the product market fit. It's
basically proving that you have a
repeatable way to create value.
And
what we do at Simply, we learn We always
listen to our users. And we saw that our
audience is not single users and this is
it. In many cases, they are part of a
household. And in that household, there
are many
passions for creative hobbies. People
want to play the guitar, people want to
sing, to cook, to draw. And we always
start by really understanding what the
pains are, what the real needs, what
limits people. Like for you, Jacob, like
it was kind of hard to learn from a
books from a non-interactive way to try
to pick up at the age of 12.
It has nothing to It doesn't know
anything about you at that point, right?
So, trying to understand what limits
people from a learning a certain hobby
and then forming a multi-disciplinary
team. We call them pods. That basically
tries to build a product offering and
nail down that value proposition that
actually meets that needs.
And we use our playbooks that we try Of
course, we have those playbooks, the
early growth playbooks and the early
customer discovery playbooks. And it's
not always the same, like you mentioned,
but we apply the same principles across
all of our apps.
And you know, first principle thinking
and we'll talk about other principles in
a second, but it's definitely a hard
task. It's not trivial to translate your
success. And today we have already
I mentioned earlier all the apps, but
Simply Piano is a market leader amongst
like 80% amongst all piano learning
apps. We're already in that market.
Simply Sing and Simply Guitar are
growing to become market leaders. And
actually Simply Draw, that only was the
recent launch, it grew 6x last year in
revenue and already at an interesting
scale, so it's not growing that slow. I
think we at this point it's really
exciting that we feel that we have
certain playbooks that we can apply for
finding product market fit with other
Not everything is success.
We don't always succeed, but we do have
some ways that allow us to repeat
the
>> You kind of know You kind of know what
works. Like you've also defined a little
bit your product or your market, right?
Like, you have the set of users and
they're J- you're talking about adjacent
users. Like, we you think about this
with features with RevenueCat. Like,
your first product market fit is hard
like cuz you're just like shooting in
the dark, but then it's like once you
have those users, you you mentioned just
talk to them and like you can kind of
figure out, you know, and then if it's
not that user, it's like somebody user
that's like almost exactly the same but
like slightly different that you just
missed. It's like, "Okay, how do I get
that?" Um and then of course there's
like
you know, the resource engine, right?
It's like the first successful PMF
tends to produce excess capital and
flow, revenue, whatever you need to
invest in the next thing, right? So
>> Yeah, I I want to dig into the
playbooks, but I was curious first, was
it always the plan to do a portfolio of
apps or did you try to put I think you
Simply Piano was first, right? And
Simply Guitar was second. Did you try
and and just like have a tab bar with
like piano and or a mini selection with
piano and guitar or did you always plan
on doing a a portfolio?
>> It was not always the plan. We did early
on we did understand that we are serving
quite many needs and it wasn't that
trivial to decide are we doing it under
one umbrella or are we doing it in
separate apps? Each one has its pros and
cons. There is no right way to go about
it.
>> And it well and I'd love to dig deep
into that because this is a real
challenge for apps because you have an
app like Calm where they, you know, make
a name for themselves in meditation and
it wasn't necessarily obvious that sleep
stories should go inside the Calm app.
Like, does that like confuse the
experience? Does it overload users? You
know, how do you onboard to two
different use cases? Like, it creates
complexity in a single app and one of
the things you generally try and do with
an app is keep it as simple and
straightforward as you can. So, let's
dig deep into like that decision-making
process of like why create the second
app and any struggles you had trying to
fit it in the first app.
>> So, everything for us always starts and
ends with what makes sense for the
users, what brings value to the users.
As you mentioned, we deeply understand
the job to be done, what they're looking
to achieve. And you're right, Jacob,
that we're looking at adjacent users,
but still, when you have a household,
when you have parents and kids and
siblings, and each one at different
intent levels, different schedule,
different availabilities, it's different
mindset altogether. So, when we
build new separate apps for for us, we
start with separate apps. It helps us
not pull weight on any product. We We
talk about this how we work. We try to
work very fast and very independent
with each product. And one of the
challenges that we discovered is on the
user acquisition front, on the growth
front, where when you have multiple apps
platform, you want to make sure that you
don't always just optimize performance
for each of the apps. You want to make
sure that those apps don't compete with
each other. You really try to understand
where your audience overlap, where they
don't overlap. And eventually, it all
goes back to the classic growth
questions. Okay, who are our users?
Where are they? How can we reach them?
With which messaging messaging?
Basically, tests to ensure that we don't
cannibalize
each other and we don't compete. And
I'll tell you even
I think mid last year, we've had a very
interesting test. I think it deserves
its own episode. It's very I will not go
into details too much, but in essence,
what we've done there, we tested for the
interaction between the apps and across
platforms, iOS and and Android. And we
basically we have
app campaigns when on the growth side
and we have web to app campaigns.
And what we did, we turned off app
campaigns on a certain geo, we turned
off web campaigns on another geo, and we
started seeing what happens to the
organic traffic, what happens to the
interactions between apps, between
platforms on the same app. And we were
able to crystallize any cannibalization
that happened or did not happen. So,
we're doing this we're measuring this
way to make sure that we don't compete,
but I'll tell you, the bottom line is
when you have a platform with multiple
apps,
it's never about perfect attribution.
>> The world's so chaotic, right? There's
just so many things that can happen,
right?
>> So chaotic, but you do need enough truth
in your CAC modeling, in your customer
acquisition cost modeling, to understand
where to put your next dollar.
This is the essence. So, it's not about
perfect attribution, but it's about
enough understanding of where you want
to put your next dollar when you spend.
>> When you launched Simply Guitar,
did you And this goes to the
cannibalization question, did you
promote it inside the piano app, or did
you use what you learned scaling Simply
Piano and do almost like a like a
parallel motion to scale Simply Guitar?
>> A parallel motion? We only do these
promotions when it really serves our
users. Meaning where we feel that
actually So, I'll tell you even an an
interesting example, we heard from many
Simply Piano users that they we
understood that when they play, they
also sing.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> So, we added
in our library of we have library of,
you know, many songs
a lot of licensed songs, we added an
indication for those pieces that we also
had the same piece in Simply Sing.
So that a person know, "Okay, I can
learn how to play this on a piano and my
spouse can increase her confidence in
singing this and we can sing and play
together or I can do it by myself." So
only when we do feel that it
it gives value to each of the apps and
we do this type of promotions. We do
have one angle and we can talk about it
uh separately where we do promote our
bundle. All of our apps.
Um but this is definitely separate. When
we start, no, we always start with
applying our independent growth
playbooks.
>> And and and it makes a lot of sense and
as you were describing your whole
business earlier, I was thinking, "Oh,
it was like a light bulb going off in my
head." Like my daughter loves to draw,
my son is playing the saxophone, my
other son learning guitar. It's like in
a family unit, you do have all these
different interests, creative interests.
And and that's where the cross-promotion
makes sense. It's interesting to hear
that it doesn't sound like that's a huge
motion for you because I mean that would
be the playbook I think most people
would expect. You have this big scaled
app, you're going to like bombard it
with like pushing people to to get the
other app, but it sounds like you take a
much more subtle approach of like, "Hey,
you're learning piano, do you also want
to sing?" And then, "Hey, if you have a
family, you can learn all the things."
How So how do you how do you present
that to the user in an effective way?
>> I think what leads us is not the growth
aspect, but rather the usage and
retention. And at the beginning Simply
Piano, we had only a single user, single
profile.
And we learned exactly to your point,
these are our households. Many people
using, sometimes several are using
Simply Piano, sometimes several using
Simply
several apps. So we introduced the
family plan and the family plan gave
flexibility for different members of the
family. Later on, it became
multi-profile
with up to five profiles and multi-app.
So, you have an offering that allows for
this flexibility. And what we saw that
when you look, of course, on a cohort
usage, you see that at any given cohort,
the segment that has the strongest
retention by far, by far, are those that
have multi-app, multi-profile accounts.
Because, like you said, you're now very
busy with hosting and podcast and stuff.
So, but your daughter, she's just went
to summer vacation. She has time to
start drawing. And your spouse is now a
she is she wants during the weekend to
learn to play the guitar. So, at any
point in time, one person of the family
will engage with the app and enjoy this
family like family plan, multi-app,
multi-profile.
>> really fits the narrative you're saying
just about the adjacencies in the
household. I mean, I think about our
Spotify family account like subscription
is like nobody's churning. You know what
I mean? Like even if Yeah, I mean, it's
just cuz like everybody gets one and
like we want our profiles to be separate
and like we pay and then we'll pay
forever, right? Like
cuz it'll never be a line that everybody
wants to cancel at the same time.
>> I agree.
>> Right. So, it makes a lot of sense.
>> What are the what are the mechanics of
presentation? Like what have you learned
over time? Like, you know, when somebody
comes into Simply Guitar, is the first
paywall they see doesn't even mention a
family plan? You just try and get them
on guitar and then like at some point in
the future, as they retain, you present
it like what what are the mechanics of
how you do that?
>> It differs. It differs not only across
apps, but also across the maturity of
the app and across time. I think it also
it's not in itself isolated. It depends
with what which expectations they came
from the ad, which campaigns we have out
there. What is our current value
proposition? And in some sometimes we
can we can discuss it as well. Sometimes
we have them soft paywalls to start with
sometimes only waiting for them to
really feel the value to appreciate the
value and then
ask them to subscribe. So it does vary
and I think that it you know, like all
of your I think all of your fair
interviews and all the companies that
you speaking with it's all about testing
always testing and what the data shows
us.
>> Do you ever advertise the family bundle
as a unit? Like do you ever
do ads that say, "Hey, your whole family
is creative. Like you know, join the
bundle." And and and for those do you
send them to the web or to the app?
>> So you touched exactly the point. We
used to be where subscription mobile
apps. So we used to be 100% ad
campaigns.
And we started enjoying
web campaigns
a couple of years ago last year. I think
we've already
I think 20% of Simply Piano revenue is
already coming from web campaigns. What
web campaigns allowed us is
of course it does allow us for better
attribution because on the app campaigns
you have ATT and this is one of the main
challenges. But in addition to better
attribution and sometimes lower fees but
again this is not our main driver. It
does allow us to first of all to
customize the experience better to our
users
and also to through that it allows us to
reach new audiences that we haven't
weren't able to reach them before that.
We can talk about this but I think the
last point is exactly to your point.
We're able to offer them this bundle
offering. When you do your app campaign
you send someone to the app store they
are now going to download Simply Sing,
Simply Draw, Simply Piano. But when they
get into some kind of a web experience
that is where you can really tell them,
"Oh, welcome to Simply. In Simply, you
can access all those apps." So, this is
where we're able to market our bundle
offer. And definitely, we we're doing it
in the web, and it's a it's really
working well for us.
>> You know, it's kind of fascinating to me
how the shape of Apple's rule how
Apple's rule shape how you develop a
business. Because in some ways, pre-ATT,
where you could deterministically see
that somebody saw an ad for Simply
Guitar, maybe in that world, it would
have made more sense to have one app
that has everything in it because you
can do an ad for Simply Guitar, you can
deterministically see what app they saw,
and then put them through an onboarding
that takes them through Simply Guitar.
If you were advertising a family plan,
you could have deterministically put
them through the family plan. And
there's a little bit of ways to hack
around that now with product pages,
where you can send the app campaign to a
different product page, and then you
know what product page they landed on,
so you can customize a little bit. But,
it's kind of fascinating to me that the
part of the draw to the web was actually
Apple's rules make it harder to do these
kinds of like customizations on it.
Um any any other comments on that or or
just lessons from the web?
>> No, so
exactly that. And and you know, many
companies are it's very popular
workflows, right? You have numerous on
one side of the extreme side, and you
have single page workflows on the other
side. And what we found that working
really well for us is the ability to
have a holistic
flow from the ad, exactly to your point,
through onboarding, and all the way to
the paywall itself. If someone clicked
on a parent ad, an ad addressed at
parents,
we can address through the onboarding
the entire pains and the entire needs of
that parent that looks for an app for
their kid.
And through that, um if I'm taking, I
think, one step back, you know, when we
browse our social networks, people on
Facebook and stuff, we're in a very
lean-back mindset. We're scrolling and
going from a lean-back mindset to an app
store and immediately asked to download
an app, it's quite a friction. And
people are, "No, I'm I'm chilling. I'm
Okay, I have an ad, but I'm not ready to
download an app and start learning a new
skill." Whereas
our web flow helps us move people from a
lean-back mindset through consideration.
>> Yeah, you ask them a basic, simple
question just to get that first, you
know,
>> Exactly. You can take 2 minutes, but
still it
>> By the end, they're going to hit the
download button, right? Cuz they've
>> Exactly. Exactly. It makes much easier
to help them understand the value
>> Right.
>> even before trying the product.
>> But even aside from that, you're just
like from a psychological perspective,
you're like waking them up a little bit,
right? Like giving them a little time to
kind of like, you know,
>> Promoting them. Exactly.
>> So, how how much of your traffic now is
going through web funnels, and have you
seen any kind of ARPU lift or or any
meaningful benefit of going through the
web?
>> About 20% of our a revenue from Simply
Piano like in the past year came from a
web flow. We did see a significant
benefits for some of our audience to go
through this web flow. We did see some a
very successful a tests where this
holistic experience from ad through a
onboarding through the paywall managed
to increase conversion significantly.
>> Are you sending free or paid? Are you
sending some users straight to the App
Store and some to web? And like, how do
you What's the Is there a rough
breakdown like when to send them where?
>> So, it depends. It dep- like each app
and its maturity level, it what is the
right creative at the right timeline,
you know, there are many considerations
um
and we have very well oiled like growth
machine uh
and that checks, you know, all the
effectiveness and performance of all of
our campaigns all the time. It allows
for better attribution so all this
personalization through the way is
something that uh
benefits us, but it does very You don't
have strict
>> Sure, so it's not like we're It's not
like we're only doing web to app. It's
just like web to app is one of the types
you know, you pair a piece of creative,
a placement plus like where it goes and
that those all three of those are being
tested and optimized.
>> Exactly. And actually um I mentioned
earlier that it allows us to get to
incremental audience. So, the web flow
uh for example, for us it uh helped us
uh
be successful with Facebook for the
first time.
>> that before.
>> For specific piano, it didn't work
before because the lean back mindset and
so So, first of all, we're able now
finally to reach out to audiences on
Facebook.
>> Yeah, I've heard that. It's just like
the the universe of people who download
apps is almost like an identity thing.
It's like I don't do apps, right? And
so, it's the same thing you got to like
prime them to be like, "No, actually you
should do apps, right?" Um and I I've
heard the same from other other apps.
>> I had this exact conversation with Leon
Sasson from
>> Yeah, that's who That's who he told me I
think this is originally, yeah.
>> He He was uh He was on the podcast
earlier this year and and he he said
exactly that that like they've seen a
ton of success, but only or almost
exclusively with the Facebook ads. And
and he he attributed it even to to age
that you know, it is typically older,
more affluent audience.
>> Or or or app native, right? Needed more
warming up. Yeah.
>> Millennials are app native. Like, you
know, the app store's been around since
I was in college, right? And so like um
and that's not true for the generations
ahead of me a little bit. So, they get
it.
>> So, we we we don't think it's We're not
insulted, but we we're that audience.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, exactly. Any any other top lessons
from from the web as far as like I mean
like that I think that's really
insightful for folks to say, okay, we
never found success on Facebook before,
let's try Webflow from Facebook and not
replicate our Instagram funnel. Any
other top lessons like that that you
think people can take away and like
where to experiment, how to experiment?
It sounds like you've done a lot of
experimentation, so I'd be curious to to
hear any other kind of top lessons
people can take away.
>> We don't look at the Webflow as a only a
place where we can save some platform
fees.
>> And usually this is one of the drivers,
right? Like attribution is one driver,
platform fees.
>> But we we learned that it's just a way
to reach incremental audiences. You just
need to understand what works with what
Webflow. What how can you communicate
your value in a way and by the way it's
also it's you don't just replicate your
App Store to web experience. It's not
about that. It's about how you can make
your users or potential users understand
some of the value they're going to get,
set up the right expectations so that
when they hit the paywall, they really
understand the value they're going to
get.
>> That that's a really different
perspective I think than a lot of people
these days. I mean, I hear from more and
more people that it's just like screw
Apple. I'm going to send all my
stuff to the web and there's this weird
hostility, but it sounds like you take a
much more pragmatic approach of like
whatever makes us the most money, that's
what we're going to do. Like how how do
you think about that?
>> So I think it's it's more than just
pragmatic. We we we look at
the platforms like Google and in Apple.
We don't look at them as the other side.
We look at them as a true partners. We
have first of all alignment of
interests.
We want to reach the most relevant
audience that
>> You have 30 30 points of alignment of
interest.
>> Exactly.
>> [laughter]
>> No, and and they want to have these
quality apps
as valuable to their users than App
stores. And they see most of the
metrics, right? But metrics are lagging
indicators. They don't always help
understand. So, we found what's working
what's working really well for us
is we work very closely with them. We
share with them our plans.
We share with them our road maps.
Our Of course, we share with them our
challenges. We ask for their help in
supporting some of the areas that we're
going.
And we found that in addition to helping
us understand where the market is going,
it also helps us really gain some
access to beta programs. It helps us
gain access to design partnerships. Some
of them I cannot even talk about here
like all the stuff, but really really
cool design partnerships that we're
we're partner with both platforms. And
basically, we're looking at the
platforms as real partners. Of course,
no one likes to pay
large fees.
>> Zero. If you ask me what what fee they
would want to pay, it's 0%, right?
That's the only logical answer.
>> [laughter]
>> We understand that okay, we're not happy
to pay, but but still we look at them as
a true partners and we have very close
collaboration relationship with
>> Yeah, I think there's it's it's like
David you're just talking about the rage
and that's like I Sweeney I mean Tim. If
you want to come on the pod, Tim, I know
you listen. Tim Sweeney, please you're
always welcome, but it's like getting
mad at the weather. You know what I
mean? Like you could get mad at the
weather. You're allowed. It's free
country. You can do what you want. But
like I don't think it's going to
increase like improve your outcomes, you
know?
>> You cannot reach audience without them.
>> Yeah, and so and I think there's there's
there's much more benefit in maximizing
the relationship, seeing the alignment,
and you know, than trying to and
you know, everybody I've talked to who
has run the experiment has like seen how
much they can they can net out of like
the the to app or sorry, app to web
flows like running their purchases. It's
interesting, but it's it's I want to say
marginal, but it's pretty close to
marginal, right? Like it's not business
changing.
>> It wasn't like it's exactly. It used to
be more, but it's not that.
>> And I get it, this is where I get
accused of being a shill for Apple
because like obviously I like IAP and
stuff, but
you know, again, it's like
>> about making the most money.
>> Right, it's testing. I you mentioned it
already, but testing. It's like, "Hey,
let's test it. Try it." You know, but I
think
>> At Revenue Cat, we're building web
funnels. We have web payments, Paddle
integration, like but it but it's about
like how do you make the most money? Not
like how do you screw Apple? It's like,
you know, send people to the web when
the web makes sense, send people the app
when the app makes sense. And but don't
like and your point is so good, Jacob,
like don't let this kind of like anger
or rage or like uh frustration
>> right? About it.
>> Justice mindset make bad business
decisions. Like make business decisions,
don't make like emotional justice driven
decisions.
>> Is it fair that Apple's a trillion
dollar company has a lot more leverage
than you? I don't know. I don't make up
the fairness rules, but it's reality,
right?
>> [laughter]
>> So,
deal with it.
>> Uh I think a lot of people listening
will be curious and you don't have to
answer if you don't, you know, have a
good answer, but how would you recommend
people build a relationship with Apple?
Often it's like a we'll call you, don't
call us kind of situation. But do you
have any any tips for working with Apple
and Google as as partners and and and
maybe even how you establish that
relationship early on?
>> I I think you know, any company with any
app developer a a certain size, but even
already at the earlier earlier sizes,
you you have an account manager
and embrace that. Embrace that. Keep
them in the loop. Fly to meet them. Make
sure that you share with them your
plans, your challenges. So, you know, in
the earlier days we used to send our
developers to WWDC with real problems
that we have with building our sound
recognition engine.
And we gave unprecedented access to
engineers in their sound system so to
help us and all of these forms
relationships and they see a partner
here that really cares to have
to great value to the users on their
platform. So we're always trying to
adopt all of the new features and adopt
all the new the recent technologies that
we can to make sure that a we give the
most quality value to our users the user
experience across of our apps.
A we have monthly meetings in even in
Simply Piano I think we have a
fortnightly meetings bi-weekly meetings
with our account manager there both in
Apple and Google. So we're always
keeping track and updating them and
learning from them where do they see
that we're not according to what they
expect in terms of benchmarks and stuff
like this.
So I think it's just embrace this
collaboration and a and keep ongoing
communication with your account manager.
>> That's more meetings than I have with
most of my reports.
>> [laughter]
>> That's really great advice though. And
speaking of those partnerships and
collaborations I know you all have been
working on Vision Pro and Android XR and
things like that. And and I'll be honest
I'm I'm a little jealous in some ways in
that you know as platforms they're so
early that I imagine you're not seeing
like a dollar-for-dollar return on your
investment in those platforms. But it's
like you're getting to be at the
forefront of this technology that will
will continue getting better and better
and it helps build that relationship.
I'm sure Apple and Google really happy
that you were on the platform and so
even if you're not getting a
dollar-for-dollar return on yeah today
you'll hopefully get it in the future
>> if it's ever a good platform, there's
there's so much alpha in being early on
a platform that just compounds. So if it
does take off like then the bet even
even if you don't invest anymore, you
know, like the bet will pay off way down
the road potentially.
>> I super agree. And you know, you touched
the
XL in variables and all this world of
augmented reality.
And for us creating learning skilling
hobbies creative hobbies
when people experience them in an
augmented reality
it's a different
game. It's a different game. Of course,
it one day everyone this is how people
will learn how to play the piano, to
play the guitar, to sing, to draw. For
us
you touched it I cannot say but
definitely some of the design
partnerships that I mentioned earlier
are around these areas and for us we
really care to be like Jacob Black you
said at the forefront of all of these
releases. Anytime that we learn that a
new device is coming up
we we try to understand okay, this form
factor, which of our products will
benefit the most from that form factor.
And it it differs across apps and across
devices.
And at that point we set up again
another pod where we are working very
fast and very closely with the platform
to make sure that we can have a product
as early as the release of that device
other. So we I agree with you. It's not
about an ROI right now with the direct
revenues, but it's definitely the
direction of the future
and we really believe in that future so
we want to be there very strongly.
>> Yeah, and I'm
such a huge vision pro fan. I mean it's
too expensive. It's too heavy, it's
expensive.
>> this. I've never used it.
>> You haven't?
>> Never put one on my face. No, I should
ask you to bring it to the offsite or
something cuz like
>> tell you I I'm I'm not kidding. I was so
I did the
the first
a build of Simply Piano on Vision Pro.
And I'm not kidding, guys.
Um seeing someone learning how to play
with Vision Pro
and I I'm like
all immersed in that experience.
And seeing how at the at the end of
their first course, they are getting a
standing ovation from a crowd in
Carnegie Hall.
And
I'm getting goosebumps. It's like
goosebumps and this guy played Ode to
Joy at the end and it feels like at the
top of the world.
You cannot get that in a non-immersive
experience. This is one of the
real um
real benefits of having this augmented
reality.
>> So, that's what's so sad to me that that
you know, rumors are Apple's kind of
slowed down and and they are working on
the Vision Air, but it's going to be you
know, delayed a year or two or whatever
it is. So, it will get lighter and
easier and better
>> of us to be
>> all the things. But, man, exactly what
you're saying is like I don't use a
Vision Pro a lot, but when I use it and
and especially and I wish Apple would
just keep leaning more into it and
putting more content out cuz when you
see the a basketball game where you can
like actually see how huge, how athletic
these I've never sat courtside at an NBA
game, but you put on the Vision Pro and
it's like holy crap. That is a totally
different experience than watching a T&N
uh you know, broadcast of a basketball
game. Um the Vision Pro they they did
all those like sample videos and then
they have a whole series with like
adventure stuff. It is insane how
immersive those experiences are and it's
like I want to use it more, but as a
platform, I wish it would have taken off
more. And and I I actually had not
downloaded the Simply Piano app on it
yet. I need to go do that this
afternoon.
>> Yeah, yeah, you should go ahead.
>> It's like, when you get that experience.
So so yeah, I'm I'm as bullish as you
are on the future of it, but it but it
we are very early innings and it's going
to take a while for the tech to catch
up.
>> They make an immersive
uh email and podcasting app, then I will
have a a big use for it. Until then, I
don't have as much time. It'd be an
aspirational
goggles for me.
>> YouTube on the uh actually
>> Oh, I'm sure. I'm sure.
>> a native app and it kind of sucks
compared to to the the one that was uh
uh the Christian's one Christian built
Juno. But man, like kicking back in a
recliner with YouTube like, you know,
100-in TV.
Even even that not immersive as far as
like the video itself wasn't immersive.
It was like an experience.
>> children, full-time job, plus VR
headsets. Not There's not enough room
for all three.
>> And and that's part of why I don't use
it very much.
>> [laughter]
>> All right, any it's no more fanboying
around the the Vision Pro. Let's get
back to
>> [laughter]
>> to the topics. Um I I did want to talk
about uh your contrarian view on monthly
plans.
Uh I know that's something Simply Piano
really focuses on, where a lot of the
industry has been pushing it harder and
harder into annual plans. So what do you
Why do you push in monthly plans and
what are your tactics around that?
>> Definitely, annual plans is the way that
most companies start with.
Especially for Simply, where learning a
new skill, learning how to play the
piano, how to express yourself in
drawing better, how to gain confidence
in singing, it takes time.
It takes time and it requires a lot of
commitment. I'm going to now dedicate
time the next few I'm going to start You
don't need much time, by the way, even
15 minutes a day, but still, you want to
start something, committing to someone.
And we saw that a committing to an
annual plan
sometimes deters our users. It's quite
another commitment of another financial
commitment. So, first of all, we it
started introducing monthly plans, and
we saw that it adds that flexibility to
our users.
So, over time, we realized, "Okay, it
can work in some aspects." And some
users find themselves feeling better
with annual plans because of the
discount, and they can their maybe their
intent is more clear. Whereas others,
they select the monthly plans, and they
are
renewing it from a month to month.
Now,
it's not that straightforward because,
of course, in an annual plan
it's it's better cash-wise, right? You
get all the annual price in advance.
This is why you companies start with it.
You have now an entire year to improve
your product before the renewal comes.
The move to monthly works only when you
have good enough retention renewals on
your monthly plans.
So, when it's justified, when you can
really move there,
it the math does work.
However,
again here, it's it's never only math
for us.
What we care a lot about is to be able
to have this fast feedback loop
between a winning test
and how it gets translated winning on
usage, and how it gets translated to its
monetary value.
So, by having monthly plans, this
feedback loop is really fast. Every
usage improvement
>> You get more renewal binary events,
right? Then trust
me.
>> You improve your usage, you improve your
retention, people use it more,
immediately translates to a better
renewal
one month renewal multiplier, and it
gets translated to revenues. So,
it does
work well for us. The monthly plan we
moved there after having a very heavily
and thoroughly tested
pricing strategy for that because it's
not you don't just do monthly plans
okay, but you need to really test
thoroughly to understand what would be
the right point with the best optimal
balance for your users and for you. And
today we have these
monthly plans many of our users are
using and some are still using annual
plans that fits them better.
>> And it makes a lot of sense. I mean
there's a reason why Netflix and big
companies like that don't do monthly
plans.
I was doing the math in my head as you
were talking a minute ago
because I've never even done this math
before is that a $25 a month
Netflix subscription is $300 a year. I
did that right, right?
>> Yeah, if I had to pay $300 for Netflix
I'd be like it's never worth that to me.
There's nothing about Netflix worth $300
to me which obviously isn't true cuz
I've been a continuous subscriber for 20
years or something, but I don't feel
that way, right?
>> I had this conversation with Seth Miller
like maybe 5 years ago. He was like look
my thesis is if you have a high
retaining app, a really you know great
app and a loyal user base the optimal
LTV will always come from a monthly, but
he was struggling to do that in his app
Rapchat, but that always stuck with me
and and and thinking about the Netflix
of the of the world like like we're
saying you wouldn't pay $300 in one drop
for Netflix and so
how are you thinking about and using the
pricing to maximize LTV and are you
seeing good LTV on your monthly?
>> Yes, yes. We wouldn't have moved if we
hadn't [laughter] seen
No, seriously it's it's
and it's not across all of our apps,
only at a certain maturity level where
we do see really strong usage for our
monthly plans,
we do this transition. And we do we do
have better LTV basically on our monthly
plans for Simply Piano. For the other
apps, we still split some of them and we
do a lot of testing ongoing, but in our
more mature apps, we feel really
comfortable about going with monthly
plans.
>> So, I'm curious on the annual plans cuz
it's something a lot of people test and
I imagine you've done a ton of testing
on it. What have you found to be a good
ratio or a good discount percentage that
does attract the people you want to
annual but then also kind of maintains a
high enough monthly price where you do
kind of maximize that LTV?
>> There's no a single percent or single
discount, but definitely the discounts a
vary I think
sometimes is 60 plus 60% or or sometimes
70 75 it depends on the plan itself. Of
course,
user psychology plays a lot here, right?
And all of our biases and anchoring and
all there are a lot of user psychology
goes into pricing. This discount level
is definitely one of the levers that we
found really beneficial to to test
basically.
>> I wonder I don't know if this played in
that you but I feel like annual versus
monthly for a lot of
developers whether they think about it
or not it's like kind of a cash flow
hack, right? It's like financial
engineering. It's basically financing
your growth with like future customer
revenues. Did that play does that play
into your philosophy here is like the
need or lack of need for operating
capital in any given time does that play
into it at all?
>> We try not to get into these things. We
it's not about financial engineering
which I agree there there can be this
way, but it's not like that for us. For
us it's a we value this cash when we try
to at the beginning of the product when
we try to use it to improve the product
over time.
At the end of the day, yes, annual plans
give you
cash benefit. But monthly plans,
we feel that it give you like some kind
of the truth about your usage.
>> What's the actual dollar There's a
dollar value to the information, right?
>> Exactly. Any retention, any usage value
that is is being really translated. So,
we we try to avoid this financial
engineering. It's not beneficial. We do
what works really well for our users and
finding the right balance of letting
those that care more about the discount
to have the annual plans and letting
those that care more about
ongoing usage on a monthly to monthly
basis, let them choose the monthly. This
is what we found works best for us.
>> I'll say it's still it's a luxury. It's
a bit of a luxury of of a company that
has time that has like the ability to
like compound and let this thing grow
cuz you see this often in like
especially in like the money Twitter
growth hacky part of like app world
where it's like, "Hey,
3-day trial to an annual plan gives you
like the most cash flow and then you can
reinvest it." And like that definitely
works, but like I it's very unlikely to
me that that is like globally optimal,
right? That is like probably just what
you need to go from zero to one which
it's the kind of point I was getting
into is like kind of sometimes is right
and that can dominate the the reasoning.
It's like, "Hey, the financial like
borrowing money from your customers at a
0% interest rate." Or actually in this
case a 40% fee, a 60 You know, you have
to give a pretty big discount to to to
do that, but like can be optimal which
which can be an input too. But I'm I'm
with you on I mean this is like both I
think emotionally and like financially,
I think like the the information flow of
of monthly. I also think it's like
flexibility is good. And so,
and and in fact like I I mean look at
Chat GPT and and now they've
differentiated and they've added annual
plans and stuff, but for the first
couple years they were just offering a
very simple $20 a month. Uh and I think
there's, you know, one it like makes it
simplifies it simplifies things for your
customers, also for you. It's a great
place to start. Uh and then also it does
feel like it comes from a position of
strength. I know this is an industry
insider, maybe it's maybe it that
doesn't affect like the average
consumer, but you go like, "Oh well, it
it goes back to the Netflix thing,
David. Like Netflix it's X dollars a
month, right? It's not like go this for
the discount and blah blah blah. They do
bundling and stuff like that, but like
it does I think in some way signal
premium to some degree, right? As a
consumer
always buy the monthly. Always buy the
monthly. Like even if it's five times
more expensive, like I'm always going to
buy the monthly. Yeah, cuz I just I'm
very bad at hedging or like pricing my
future attention span, right? So like I
just I pay I pay more for the
flexibility, right?
>> So interesting because I'm as a parent,
I feel that
I know it's contradicting any logic, but
I find myself buying annual plans for my
kids sometimes because my inspiration I
think of course they will use it. Of
course
>> on the app.
>> Use this math app like for a little
>> You're making an investment.
>> After six months I realize, "Oh, I have
a subscription here."
>> Goes back Goes back to testing, right?
Like every every user has different
motivations and they just you have to
test for the aggregate.
>> Have you ever experimented with weekly
plans? I mean typically they are used
a lot of apps that use them aren't high
retention and so it's kind of like
maximizing the LTV over a very short
time span.
>> uh it's the monthly it's the monthly
thesis at the limit, right? It's like
how do you maximize maximize?
>> For Simply Piano and then maybe
especially the the bundle, five bucks a
a week, you
know, I don't know exactly what your
your um
you know, plans are for for the bundle,
but five or 10 bucks a week is probably
a very reasonable price for the bundle
where you get all the apps and
everything like that. And then I did
hear from I heard from a guy at Apple,
he since left, so
I feel more comfortable saying this. I
pushed back really hard on on weekly
subscriptions like a decade ago. And the
conversation with him was like, Apple,
from their, you know, talking to users
and everything like that, they do see,
especially like in emerging markets and
stuff, that a weekly plans are that
people do like them because it gives you
that like, you know, you're not for
people who like $50 a month is a lot. If
they get $50 a month of value, but
spread that out, $10 or $40 a month of
value, but they spread that out, $10 a
week, that's actually a nice, even kind
of what we were talking about with the
cash flow of monthly, it's like taking
that to the limit of like, I'm just
going to pay $10 a week instead of $40 a
month, instead of
$480 a year. So, of all the apps, I
think a bundle with all your apps
probably is worth 10 bucks a week. But
So, with all that said, I'm
>> [laughter]
>> I'm curious if you've done any any
experimentation on it, and then what you
learned doing that.
>> It's a great question, because I think
I'm always that I always like to look at
the extremes. Yes, weekly reduces the
friction even further, right? You don't
even think about $5 that you're
how much your coffee cost you this
morning. However, when you look, and I'm
always sorry for always going back to
our users and how they use our app.
You want to learn a new skill. This
takes time.
You cannot judge yourself every week.
Oh, do I already know that I will play
the piano? Am I more confident in
singing already? No. This takes time.
So, having Yes, it's a low friction, but
having this
on every week, every Are you sure you
want to pay? Are you sure you want to
pay? Are you sure?
It's not that easy. So, I think
when we think of usage, the longer plans
plans make more sense for the how people
learn new skills.
However, you're right that there is this
other side of reducing friction upon
checkout. We've tested it in some of the
apps not in the bundle, in some apps,
but right now we're not offering any
discounts.
>> And that says a lot. And I love your
point, too, that even on a monthly there
is a little bit of
like commitment. Like, "Hey, I paid 40
bucks or 30 bucks or whatever the price
is and I'm going to I'm going to, you
know, make use of that. I'm going to
actually, you know,
>> build the habit.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> And and finances are an incentive to
build that habit.
>> Exactly. Exactly. [laughter]
>> As you've scaled the business, what have
you done as far as localization? I know
so many apps, you know, so dependent on
the US and so focused on the US, but it
does seem like as companies scale, they
have more resources and time to invest
in other countries and and then
actually, you know, start to make it
work. Where people more focused on the
US just throw a price out there and it
doesn't happen.
Um so so what are you seeing
internationally uh for your products?
>> I think for many companies localization
or expanding to other geos is quite a
high potential low-risk growth engine,
right? It's There's not so much risk, of
course. You will localize your app to a
different culture, people will feel more
comfortable using it. However, it's not
that trivial.
And for us, we always look uh
we've done two things that mainly work
well for us in terms of localization.
First of all, when you localize to a
different country or you want to not
only convert your currency there, but
you really want to localize the pricing
which makes sense. So, we created our
own pricing index, like our own like a
Big Mac index, similar concept, that
takes into account not like similarly to
the Big Mac, like the purchase power in
that geo, but also other considerations
that we can refer to when people think
about using learning how to play a
musical instrument or
learning how to draw. This is one thing
that we've done and we applied this
pricing scheme across all geos, we saw
significant ARPU increase
significant dramatic ARPU increase. In
some geos we were surprised that it
didn't work, but we had to adapt there.
But in the vast majority of geos it
really worked really well for us.
>> What was the initial
hypothesis or factors that went into the
first test and then you know, how many
geos did you go into where where your
assumption on price was wrong and you
had to change it? Like did you start
with the Big Mac Index and like work
your way back or like how how did you
actually cuz this is something I hear a
lot of people asking about actually. So
this is a question I get for revenue cat
all the time is like you guys have all
the data you should create a pricing
suggestion table, but it's not that
simple. Different products have
different like willingness to pay. So
what were the the kind of factors that
went into your decision making around
that that starting price when you were
focusing on a new geo?
>> We start always with the leanest way
possible.
We try to
So I think at the beginning I'm talking
about the years ago we implemented the
Big Mac as itself index and then we
evolved it over the years. In that case
we didn't test one geo after the other
we just defined we modeled pricing
strategy with the same principle across
all geos. We rolled it out as a test and
we saw which worked and we optimized it
over time.
And of course pricing test also you need
to update your pricing not only as you
your ARPU matures, but also as you reach
new audiences as you the time passes and
it is so it it is something that we
continuously work on, but I I think you
touched also on the way that we test
stuff and you it does touch the the the
second part of how we localize.
And basically localization, you know,
it's more than just translation. In our
case, we localize
the content, the songs of that country,
all the translation of the app, all the
app store, and of course the pricing and
and the creatives as well. But if you
want to localize to a specific country,
you cannot do all this work only to find
out that
it's not as you hoped for.
So, what the principle that leads us is
we want to make sure that whatever we
do, we do it with the highest quality.
With localization, it's all about trust,
right? If you try to localize your
first-time user experience, but you
don't continue to localize deeper into
the product, people lose trust. If you I
don't know if
any of you if you tried to localize to
Germany, it's
Germany is an interesting example where
the way you address people changes.
Um so, it the consistency, the way that
you
localize throughout your app, the way
that you the UX looks, the currency,
everything, you need to make sure that
whatever you do, even if it's a limited
scope, you do it at the highest
standards. You don't want to lose trust.
You want to make sure that you set up
the right expectations with the users.
And uh once you gain confidence in that
direction, then you can go all in and do
full localization. But we don't do it to
begin with. You we all because it's
okay, it's not the riskiest part of
growing a product. It's something that
is quite sure. When we need, we expand
to to other markets.
>> I'm going to I'm going to clip that
whole segment, and anybody who tells me,
"We tried Germany. Like we we localized
the price. We did a couple of things,
and like we just can't crack Germany.
I'm going to send them that clip because
cracking international markets really is
a ton of work and it is an investment
and you have to think about it like that
because if you just change the price and
expect to crack a market, like that's
not how you crack a market. Any other
top lessons or like interesting geos
where there were counterintuitive things
that you learned that that maybe you
could share and like at least get people
a head start.
>> So yeah, actually
one of the most mind-blowing
learnings that we've had at some point
at Simply Piano we decided we we already
had been translated to
11 languages and we decided we want to
go to the first geo where we're going to
really localize, not translation but
fully localization.
Uh so like we always do we created a
very thoughtful and deep model that
estimated the potential of each geo in
terms of what might be the upside in
that geo, the incremental audience and
incremental ARPU, but also what is our
confidence that we can really meet that
potential. So we landed on a Japan.
Japan for us, for Simply Piano, was our
first deep localization that we wanted
to go. So we started like I mentioned,
we're highly confident that we can
really reach this potential. We
localized some Japanese, some you know,
songs like from anime and we all the UX
was changed and App Store creatives,
everything was translated and localized,
of course currency,
to Japanese.
And all the metrics started growing.
Great, as expected, except for one
metric, the checkout conversion, the
paywall conversion.
It did not move, even on the contrary,
it even decreased.
And we didn't know why. Like, come on,
it's like we did everything properly.
Uh we brought in a country manager,
Japanese country manager, a great guy,
and he reviewed our flow.
And he told us, "Guys, you're not uh
treating the paywall properly."
Uh you know, us, we're used to all the
best practices in paywalls, you know,
make it very clear, least disruptive.
You want to minimize the details on the
paywall. You want some social proof. You
want some things that Overall, you want
a very clean paywall.
The Japanese 180°
opposite. They expect very detailed
story of the company,
of the founders, of our values, of all
the things that you're frustrated that
no one reads, they want to read.
>> [laughter]
>> All the social quotes and all a lot of
colors. I I'm telling you you you can't
even believe. We had a very long
one-pager that they scrolled and
scrolled and
conversion skyrocketed.
>> Wow.
>> So, it it it told us that, you know,
in in any localization, best practices
can take you up to a certain point,
but you really need to understand the
intricacies and delicacies of each
user that you're serving and the the
audience and what really bothers them.
So, it was a great lesson in
localization.
>> Such such a great insight. Uh well, as
we wrap up, I'm going to ask you the
three questions I now ask every guest.
Uh kicking it off with uh what's the
most impactful experiment or change
you've implemented this year, your
biggest win?
>> I can talk about um
a fantastic test that our a product team
in Simply Draw did where
it's uh
of course we didn't talk about how we
use AI across all of our
work, but we use it very of course
extensively and and heavily, and they
used AI to bring the drawing that the
kid was just finished drawing, bring it
to life. And this gave the kids
excitement and something to be proud of
that they were running to their parents
to be proud, "Look what I did."
Now, the parents at that point, what did
they see?
They saw that, "Hey, this app that my
kid is using is not just spending time
on another app. It's like very positive
screen time. They could see the value of
the app."
So, when we introduced this during
first-time user experience, it really
increased output because parents could
really understand, "Hey, this product
worth me investing in it."
Uh so, this was an amazing, I think, win
from our product team. And it was
something that you know, they do these
social shares where they they share
organically, parents share organically
on Instagram and like, "Look what my kid
8-year-old kid did." And it's a delight.
It's a delight. You see them, it's it's
really a fantastic way to see.
>> Have you found that feature to perform
well as an ad creative? Like once you
launch that feature and saw it really
take off, are you actually using that in
ads? Cuz that sometimes that's a fun way
to like get a really high-performing ad
is to find that kind of magic moment.
>> Exactly. So, we are doing it
and we are doing it and you're you're
spot-on. Many times, many of our
creatives are being inspired by real
usage that happens in in features that
are really beneficial to our users, we
turn them into ads.
>> Yeah, very cool. All right, what is the
worst experiment or change you made in
the past year? Your biggest fail of the
past year?
>> I I knew that you're going to send me
you're going to ask me these questions
because you're asking it in every
episode and I am a big fan of
your podcast and it's when I thought
about it I said first of all so many to
choose from, right? We're we're a
testing company, we always test and so
many failures. But I think one that
taught us a lot was what we call a
premium awareness test. Where in Simply
Piano it we introduced a soft paywall
at the end of onboarding.
And we wanted to see maybe it will be
appealing to the onboarding will be
enough for people to already commit.
This test was fantastic significantly on
ARPU.
It was a great great win, we celebrated
it. Um
And we we were proud of it and we
enjoyed it for months and months
only to realize after
lots of months
that after many months that
um
a actually the users that subscribed to
through that soft paywall
were using our touch experience.
Meaning they don't necessarily have any
piano at home or any keyboard at home.
They only enjoyed uh we have some couple
of touch courses on Simply Piano. So
they only
they enjoyed playing it but but they
signed up for a year. We don't have any
value for a year. So this is not the
audience that we're looking for.
So we were
I I we're so bummed about it because it
No, it wasn't winning as we thought.
But then
we had a second lesson.
Then when we looked deeper into the
deeper segmentation we realized that
actually one segment did find real value
in it. And this was the segment of kids.
Because kids they love to really play
and play the same songs again and again
and again. They just enjoy it. And it
builds them, it gives them time until
they're ready to get their first small
keyboard at home. So, we ended up a
a
taking it off our adults, and they all
the accounts with only adults uh
profiles, and we kept the soft paywall
for those accounts that have kids
profiles on.
And uh this works well for us, but
um it started as a like um
really un like a very surprising loss
that they like that we had for that
test.
>> Yeah, that's fascinating. All right,
last question as we wrap up, and this is
a fill-in-the-blank. Growth would be
easier if
>> I think if um
we could
uh
impact users during awareness and
consideration phases
uh without hurting their privacy needs.
You know, at the end of the day, ATT is
there for a reason, right? Privacy is
good.
It does prevent us to customize the
experience
uh already from awareness and
consideration phases. So, I think if we
could magically do that, not hurt your
privacy, but still be able
to fully customize our uh growth
activities and creatives for you,
uh it could have been easier.
>> Yeah, it's especially hard for y'all
targeting kids. The kid the rules around
kids uh and different and a lot of it is
is like governmental regulations and
stuff like that that you have to abide
by.
>> And we all know just how safe and
wholesome the App Store is for kids
thanks to those regulations. As parents,
we all know that's been done. Thank you
very much, Apple, for protecting us.
Sorry.
>> All right. Well, this was so much fun. I
really enjoyed the conversation. I think
there's so much uh people can take away,
experiments they can go do based on this
conversation. So, thank you so much for
sharing and opening up. Any anything you
want to share as we wrap up? Any uh
roles you're hiring for? Anything you
want to shout out?
>> So, first of all, it was a great fun.
Thank you so much for having me and and
it's a a real honor to be here. I I
think for us, I I I mentioned it
earlier, it's we're always hiring and we
want our
on our website our the positions we're
looking for, it's always about a
being able to reach almost every
household around the world
and help them fulfill their long life
dream sometimes of playing piano,
playing the guitar, singing more
confidently, or drawing a more
expressively. And
I think we're we're thinking big, we're
thinking we're we're on our way there.
And I hope to be able to, you know, to
speak with you guys maybe in a year, 2
years time and to talk about more
products and wider audience and more
than anything more lessons that we have
gathered.
It's really exciting time.
>> Awesome. Thank you so much for joining
us. This is so fun.
>> [music]
>> Thanks so much for listening.
If you have a minute, please leave a
review in your favorite podcast player.
You can also stop by chat.subclub.com
to join our private community.
>> [music]